[
  {
    "queryProperty": "type",
    "question": "What meal type are you looking for?",
    "response": ["breakfast", "lunch/dinner", "dessert", "other"],
    "other": {
      "queryProperty": "type",
      "question": "if other",
      "response": ["snack", "soup", "bread", "salad", "drink"]
    }
  },
  {
    "queryProperty": "maxReadyTime",
    "question": "maxReadyTime?",
    "response": ["15", "30", "60", "none"]
  },
  {
    "queryProperty": "cuisine",
    "question": "what type of cuisine?",
    "response": ["americas", "european", "asian", "south american", "other"],
    "americas": {
      "queryProperty": "cuisine",
      "question": "what type of american",
      "response": ["american", "Southern", "Cajun"]
    },
    "european": {
      "queryProperty": "cuisine",
      "question": "european",
      "response": ["british", "italian", "french", "german", "greek"]
    },
    "asian": {
      "queryProperty": "cuisine",
      "question": "asian",
      "response": ["chinese", "korean", "japanese", "thai", "viet", "indian"]
    },
    "south american": {
      "queryProperty": "cuisine",
      "question": "south american",
      "response": ["mexican", "Latin American", "Caribbean"]
    },
    "other": {
      "queryProperty": "cuisine",
      "question": "other",
      "response": ["Jewish", "African", "Mediterranean"]
    }
  },
  {
    "queryProperty": "intolerances",
    "question": "intolerances",
    "response": ["peanut", "gulten", "dairy", "seafood", "none"]
  },
  {
    "queryProperty": "diet",
    "question": "diet",
    "response": ["Vegetarian", "Vegan", "Ketogenic", "Pescetarian", "none"]
  },
  {
    "queryProperty": "maxCalories",
    "question": "maxCalories",
    "response": ["200", "500", "none"]
  }
]
